web2mail.com 2002-12-15

# Web2Mail.com - Privacy policy

Advertise your  
business here  
with Web2Mail  

Advertise your  
business here  
with Web2Mail  

|   
---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
[<< Return to previous page](javascript:history.go\(-1\))

### Web2Mail privacy policy

This site is operated by Web2Mail Ltd (company number 3857685 whose registered office is at Roman House, 296 Golders Green Road, London, NW11 9PT UK). All correspondence should be sent to [info@web2mail.com](mailto:info@web2mail.com) or Web2Mail Ltd. 

Your privacy is very important to you and to us. Our continued success depends on the trust of our customers. 

We store your email address to send to you regular updates of pages from the world wide web which you have elected to receive at times selected by you. In addition, if you send to us an email with a one-off request either for a web page to be sent to you or for a search to be made using your search words, we store your email address to deal with your specific request. We hold details on our database of sites to which you have subscribed or about which you have made a request. 

We also use your email address to send to you from time to time a news letter with information about new products and services that are likely to be of interest to you. We will only send you this message if you give us your permission when you subscribe to Web2Mail. If you choose not to receive our news letters we will respect your privacy and guarantee that we only send you the regular emails with the web pages which you have requested. 

We use your information to create information about you which we use to identify your preferences. This enables us to personalise offers, advertisements and services to suit your individual preferences. 

We use cookies to recognise your user name when you sign in. The use of cookies means that you do not have to enter your user name more than once, thereby saving time while you enter our site. We only use cookies for your convenience whilst you are on our site. The cookies simply make your use of our site easier, but if you prefer to use the site without utilising cookies, your browser can be set not to accept them at all. Information stored in cookies cannot be accessed by other web sites. 

We promise: 

  * We will never disclose your email address or any other personal data to any third party save as required by applicable law 
  * We will never send you emails without your permission 
  * We will delete all data capable of identifying you personally from our records if you completely unsubscribe from the Web2Mail service. 

This site is hosted in the USA. This means that your data will be exported out of the European Union to a country which does not have a data protection law. However, Web2Mail has sole control over the content. The host does not monitor, restrict or use your data in any way. Tape backups are kept under lock and key. The host may use these backups where necessary to ensure that the site remains in operation. 

This site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those sites or of sites to which you subscribe using Web2Mail - this privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this site. 

Any material changes in the way we use your personal data will be described in future versions of this privacy policy. By subscribing to the Web2Mail service you agree that the privacy policy current at the time of your most recent subscription or request shall apply to all information we hold about you, whether given to us at the time of that subscription or on earlier occasions. We will notify you of any material changes in our privacy policy by email. 

If you have any questions or comments about our privacy policy or the data which we hold about you, please mail info@web2mail.com By ticking the box which states you have read this privacy policy, you consent to our use of your information in the ways described above. 

* * *

© 2002 Web2Mail Ltd. All rights reserved. Use of this site is subject to the site terms and privacy policy.
